# **BOHDAN FEDOROV**

## JS DEVELOPER MIDDLE



#### About me

I am a professional developer with skills in problem-solving, strong communication abilities, and the ability to work well in a team. My analytical skills allow me to effectively develop solutions for complex tasks, and my project management and time management skills help ensure successful project execution and priority setting.

Overall, my non-coding skills complement my technical expertise and make me a successful developer capable of achieving high results in my profession and working effectively in a team environment.

#### Contact info

• E email: bogdanfedorov@gmail.com

phone: +380 97 168 28 25

• \* telegram: https://t.me/FedorovBohdan

#github: https://github.com/bogdanfedorov

### **EDUCATION**

- College of Information Systems and Technologies (2014-2017)
- WSPA Engineer Lublin, Poland (2017-2020)
  - Mobile and Web Technology: JAVA, C#, JS, Python, SQL DB, business process analysis, UX/UI mobile,

### **EXPERIENCE**

- Freelance (2018-2021) Lublin, Poland
  - o Trainee Intern Junior
- Yalantis (2021-2022) Kiev, Ukraine
  - Junior(+)
- Lampa Software(2022-2023) Vinnica, Ukraine
  - Junior(+) Middle

#### **LANGUAGES**

- English (B1)
- Ukrainian (Native)
- Polish (C1)

# KNOWLEDGE

Backend		Front-end	
JavaScript (JS/TS)		HTML/CSS/JS	
Node.js		Vite	
Nest.js		Next.js	
Express.js		React.js and Vue.js	
Apollo Server (GraphQL)		Apollo Client (GraphQL)	
Automation testing (jest)		Styles: Tailwind	
Documentation (swagger , jsdoc, ts interfaces)			
Storage: Redis, MongoDB, Postgres, SQLite			
Orm: TypeORM, Mongoose			
Other skills			
Code reviewing	Business analytics		Microservices an monolit arhitecture
System design	Solid principles		Linux
Docker	Git		Figma